[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
As we saw in our plot, stochastic gradient tends to oscillate around the optimum.
وكما لاحظنا في الرسومات لدينا، فإن التدرج العشوائي يميل للتذبذب حول المثالية.
And so you should never trust the last parameter it finds, unfortunately.
ولهذا لا يمكنك الوثوق أبدًا في المعلمة الأخيرة التي يحصل عليها، لسوء الحظ.
Gradient will eventually stabilize on the optimal solution.
وسيقوم التدرج بالاستقرار على الحل الأمثل في النهاية.
So even though it takes a hundred times longer or
حتى لو استغرق حدوث ذلك وقت أكثر بـ 100 ضعف أو أكثر،
more, like was shown in this example, so
كما هو موضح في هذا المثال،
if you look at the x-axis a hundred times more time to converge, you get there.
ولهذا، إذا نظرت غلى محور X لمئات من المرات، ومرة أخرى للتقارب فستصل لهناك،
And you feel really good when you get there.
وستشعر بحالٍ جيدة عند الوصول لهناك.
Stochastic gradient, when you think it converged, is really that it's
وبالنسبة للتدرج العشوائي، عندما تعتقد أنه قد تقارب،
oscillating around the optimum, and that can lead to bad practical behavior.
وهو في الواقع يتذبذب حول المثالية ويمكن أن يؤدي ذلك إلى سلوك سيئ.
So for example here, I'm just giving you some numbers,
ولهذا بالنسبة للمثال هنا، فأنا أعطيك فقط بعض الأرقام،
say w at iteration 1000 might look really, really bad.
قائلاً أن w على تكرار يساوي 1000، قد يبدو الأمر سيئًا للغاية.
But maybe W at iteration 1005 looks really, really good and needs some kind of
ولكن w على تكرار يساوي 1005 يبدو جيدًا تمامًا
approach to minimize the risk of picking a really bad one or a really good one.
وبحاجة لطريق ما لتقليل خطر اقتطاف واحدة جيدة تمامًا أو أخرى سيئة تمامًا.
And there is a very simple technique which works really well in practice, and
ويوجد طريقة بسيطة للغاية والتي تعمل بشكل جيد للغاية في الممارسة،
theoretically is what you should do.
ونظريًا هي ما يجب عليك فعله.
So all the theorems require something like this.
ولذلك، فإن جميع النظريات بحاجة لمثل ذلك.
And what it says is.
وما توضحه هو،
When you are outputting w hat, your final self-coefficient,
عندما تنتج Ŵ، وكذلك المعامل الذاتي،
you don't use the last value, w(t),
فأنت لا تستخدم القيمة الأخيرة (w(t،
capital T, you use the average of all the values that you've computed.
بل تستخدم متوسط جميع القيم التي قمت بحسابها.
All the coefficients you computed along the way.
وجميع المعاملات التي قمت بحسابها,.
So, what I'm showing here is what your algorithm should output as it's fitting
ولهذا، ما أوضحه هنا، هو ما يجب أن تنتجه الخوارزمية
the solution to make some predictions in the real world.
لتناسب الحل للقيام ببعض التنبؤات في العالم الحقيقي.
>> [MUSIC]
>> [موسيقى]